Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2007
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- JIB-07, June 2007, IV.; 1 CD-ROM (46 image files in TIFF format)
  - John Aylward rehearsing his End of Winter with Rin Ozaki, Charles Haupt, and Tony Arnold, Original file name: John Aylward END OF WINTER.tif (Image-file cd04_33)
  - Charles Haupt, Tony Arnold, John Aylward, and Rin Ozaki, Original file name: John Aylward stud.composer END OF WINTER.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-028 (Image-file cd04_34)
  - June in Buffalo students and auditors, 2007: Jacques Baldasari, Matthew Barnson, Daniel Van Hassel,S. Anthony Amstutz, Jeff Silva, Daniel Blake, and Aubrey Byerly, Original file name: June in Buffalo 07.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-113 (Image-file cd04_35)
  - June in Buffalo students and auditors 2007: Jenece Gerber, Dominique Schafer, Eric Roth, Eliza Brown, Lee Weisert, Michael McBride, James Ogburn, Ya-Ting Lee, and Patrick Castillo, Original file name: June in Buffalo 2007.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-114 (Image-file cd04_36)
  - David Felder looking at score with student composers, Original file name: Lecture David Felder--.tif (Image-file cd04_37)
  - Student composers looking at David Felder score during rehearsal, Original file name: LECTURE David Felder-.tif (Image-file cd04_38)
  - David Felder presenting lecture in Slee Hall, Original file name: Lecture David Felder.tif (Image-file cd04_39)
  - Composer Lee Weisert (center) with members of the Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble, Matthew Jenkins, Justin DeHart, Johannes Fischer, and Fabio Oliveira, rehearsing Weisert's composition, Rockaby, Original file name: Lee Weisert with RFBF.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-116 (Image-file cd04_40)
  - Student composers in David Felder masterclass, Original file name: Masterclass David Felder.tif (Image-file cd04_41)
  - Student composers looking at David Felder score during rehearsal, Original file name: Score David Felder.tif (Image-file cd04_42)
  - Composer Christian Baldini with conductor Harold Rosenbaum and members of the New York Virtuoso Singers rehearsing Baldini's composition, Two adoration motets, Original file name: The NY Virtuoso Singers Christian Baldini_ Harold Rosenbaum.tif (Image-file cd04_43)
  - Composer Christian Baldini with conductor Harold Rosenbaum and members of the New York Virtuoso Singers rehearsing Baldini's composition, Two adoration motets, Original file name: The NY Virtuoso Singers.tif (Image-file cd04_44)
  - Conductor Harold Rosenbaum rehearsing with the New York Virtuoso Singers and instrumentalists, Original file name: THE NY VIRTUOSO SINGERS___.tif (Image-file cd04_45)
  - Tony Arnold, Paolo Cavallone, and Christian Baldini, Original file name: Tony Arnold Christian Baldini _Paolo Cavallone-stud.comp.jpg Converted file name: JIB2007-005 (Image-file cd04_46)
- Steve Reich rehearsal, June 2007, V.; 1 CD-ROM (30 image files in TIFF format)
  - Steve Reich and Brad Lubman during rehearsal of Reich's Tehillim with Slee Sinfonietta, Original file name: --Steve Reich Brad Lubman.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-066 (Image-file cd05_01)
  - Steve Reich talking with conductor Brad Lubman, with soprano Jolle Greenleaf, Caleb Burhans, and Martha Cluver, Original file name: -Steve Reich Brad Lubman Caleb Burhans Martha Cluver.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-074 (Image-file cd05_02)
  - Conductor Brad Lubman and composer Steve Reich, Original file name: 003 Brad Lubman-Steve Reich 07.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-073 (Image-file cd05_03)
  - Conductor Brad Lubman examining score of Charles Wuorinen's Percussion Quartet with percussionists Jason Treuting, Jon Hepfer, and Fabio Oliveira, Original file name: 003 Cond.Brad Lubman explaining Wuorinen music.tif (Image-file cd05_04)
  - Brad Lubman conducting vocalists and the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal of Steve Reich's Tehillim, Original file name: 009 TEHILLIM by Steve Reich.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-044 (Image-file cd05_05)
  - Brad Lubman conducting vocalists and the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal of Steve Reich's Tehillim, Original file name: 011TEHILLIM by Steve Reich.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-045 (Image-file cd05_06)
  - Conductor Brad Lubman examining score of Charles Wuorinen's Percussion Quartet with percussionists Jason Treuting, Jon Hepfer, and Fabio Oliveira, Original file name: 023 conductor Brad Lubman explaining Wuorinen music.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-048 (Image-file cd05_07)
  - Brad Lubman conducting vocalists and the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal of Steve Reich's Tehillim, Original file name: 025 TEHILLIM by Steve Reich.tif (Image-file cd05_08)
  - Brad Lubman conducting vocalists and the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal of Steve Reich's Tehillim, Original file name: 027 TEHILLIM by Steve Reich.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-046 (Image-file cd05_09)
  - Conductor Brad Lubman and composer Steve Reich at rehearsal of Tehillim, Original file name: 031 Brad Lubman -Steve Reich.tif (Image-file cd05_10)
  - Steve Reich and Brad Lubman during rehearsal of Reich's Tehillim with Slee Sinfonietta, Original file name: 033 Brad Lubman -Steve Reich.tif (Image-file cd05_11)
  - Steve Reich and Brad Lubman during rehearsal of Reich's Tehillim with Slee Sinfonietta, Original file name: 035 Brad Lubman Steve Reich 07.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-069 (Image-file cd05_12)
  - Conductor Brad Lubman examining score of Charles Wuorinen's Percussion Quartet with percussionists Jason Treuting, Jon Hepfer, and Fabio Oliveira, Original file name: conductor Brad Lubman with Wuorinen score.tif (Image-file cd05_13)
  - Rehearsal of Steve Reich's Daniel Variations, Original file name: Daniel Variations by Steve Reich Rehears.JIB 07 002.tif (Image-file cd05_14)
  - Slee Sinfonietta members rehearsing Steve Reich's Daniel Variations, Original file name: Daniel Variations by Steve Reich Rehears.JIB 07 004.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-061 (Image-file cd05_15)
  - Slee Sinfonietta members rehearsing Steve Reich's Daniel Variations, Original file name: Daniel Variations by Steve Reich Rehears.JIB 07 005.tif (Image-file cd05_16)
  - Slee Sinfonietta members rehearsing Steve Reich's Daniel Variations, Original file name: Daniel Variations by Steve Reich Rehears.JIB 07 007.tif (Image-file cd05_17)
  - Slee Sinfonietta members rehearsing Steve Reich's Daniel Variations, Original file name: Daniel Variations by Steve Reich Rehears.JIB 07 010.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-062 (Image-file cd05_18)
  - Slee Sinfonietta members rehearsing Steve Reich's Daniel Variations, Original file name: Daniel Variations by Steve Reich Rehears.JIB 07 011.tif (Image-file cd05_19)
  - Slee Sinfonietta members rehearsing Steve Reich's Daniel Variations, Original file name: Daniel Variations by Steve Reich Rehears.JIB 07 015.tif (Image-file cd05_20)
  - Slee Sinfonietta members rehearsing Steve Reich's Daniel Variations, Original file name: Daniel Variations by Steve Reich Rehears.JIB 07 017.tif (Image-file cd05_21)
  - Composers Steve Reich and David Felder, Original file name: David Felder- Steve Reich.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-077 (Image-file cd05_22)
  - Steve Reich talking with conductor Brad Lubman, with Jolle Greenleaf, Caleb Burhans, and Martha Cluver, Original file name: Steve Reich Brad Lubman Caleb Burhans Martha Cluver.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-075 (Image-file cd05_23)
  - Steve Reich and Brad Lubman during rehearsal of Reich's Tehillim with Slee Sinfonietta, Original file name: Steve Reich Brad Lubman---.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-068 (Image-file cd05_24)
  - Steve Reich and Brad Lubman during rehearsal of Reich's Tehillim with Slee Sinfonietta, Original file name: Steve Reich Brad Lubman.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-067 (Image-file cd05_25)
  - Singers during rehearsal of Steve Reich's composition, Tehillim, Original file name: TEHILLIM by Steve Reich Conducter Brad Lubman 007.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-071 (Image-file cd05_26)
  - Singers and clappers during rehearsal of Steve Reich's composition, Tehillim, Original file name: TEHILLIM by Steve Reich Conducter Brad Lubman 014.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-072 (Image-file cd05_27)
  - Singers and clappers during rehearsal of Steve Reich's composition, Tehillim, Original file name: TEHILLIM by Steve Reich Conducter Brad Lubman 016.tif (Image-file cd05_28)
  - Brad Lubman conducting the Slee Sinfonietta in rehearsal of Steve Reich's Tehillim, Original file name: TEHILLIM by Steve Reich Conducter Brad Lubman 020.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-047 (Image-file cd05_29)
  - Steve Reich and Brad Lubman during rehearsal of Reich's Tehillim with Slee Sinfonietta, Original file name: x`Steve Reich Brad Lubman.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-070 (Image-file cd05_30)
- Reich & Reynolds, RFBF, June 2007, VI.; 1 CD-ROM (18 image files in TIFF format)
  - Steve Reich gesturing during lecture, Original file name: -Steve Reich b-w.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-063 (Image-file cd06_01)
  - Steve Reich gesturing during lecture, Original file name: -Steve Reich.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-064 (Image-file cd06_02)
  - Steve Reich gesturing during lecture, Original file name: .Steve Reich lecture.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-065 (Image-file cd06_03)
  - Arditti String Quartet in rehearsal onstage in Slee Hall, Original file name: Arditti Quartet==.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-002 (Image-file cd06_04)
  - Conductor Brad Lubman with composer Steve Reich, Original file name: Brad Lubman and Steve Reich at reheasal.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-043 (Image-file cd06_05)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds and percussionist Gustavo Aguilar, member of Red Fish Blue Fish percussion ensemble, Original file name: composer Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-086 (Image-file cd06_06)
  - John Harbison with conductor Harold Rosenbaum rehearsing Harbison's But Mary Stood, with Calvin Weirsma and Deborah Wong, violins, and Lois Martin, viola, Original file name: cond. Harold Rosenbaum comp.J.Harbison rehearsing.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-024 (Image-file cd06_07)
  - John Harbison and conductor Harold Rosenbaum during rehearsal of Harbison's But Mary Stood, with Deborah Wong, violin, Lois Martin, viola, and Chris Finckel, violoncello, Original file name: John Harbison_Harold Rosenbaum cond. The NY Virtuoso Singers.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-025 (Image-file cd06_08)
  - Steve Reich and David Felder onstage during lecture/discussion, Original file name: Lecture Steve Reich with David Felder.tif (Image-file cd06_09)
  - Composers Steve Reich and David Felder at a lecture given by them, Original file name: Reich lecture.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-079 (Image-file cd06_10)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Greg Stuart, Justin DeHart, Gustavo Aguilar, and Robert Esler rehearsing Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: RFBF rehearsing SANCTUARY_Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-060 (Image-file cd06_11)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble in rehearsal, Original file name: RFBF rehearsing.tif Converted file name: duplicate (Image-file cd06_12)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with technical assistant, Ian Saxton, and members of the Red Fish Blue Fish percussion ensemble, Greg Stuart, Robert Esler, Justin DeHart, and Gustavo Aguilar, Original file name: RFBF with composer Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-088-dup (Image-file cd06_13)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with percussionist Robert Esler and the Waterphone used in the Oracle section of his composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Roger Reynolds with THE ORACLE.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-087 (Image-file cd06_14)
  - Composers Steve Reich and David Felder, Original file name: Steve Reich and David Felder lecture.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-078 (Image-file cd06_15)
  - Steve Reich with composer Daniel Van Hassel, Original file name: Steve Reich_stud.composer Dan vanHassle_interviewer.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-076 (Image-file cd06_16)
  - Roger Reynolds talks with Steven Schick, director the Red Fish Blue Fish percussion ensemble, Original file name: Steve Schick with composer Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-084 (Image-file cd06_17)
  - Conductor Harold Rosenbaum rehearsing John Harbison's composition, But Mary stood, with the New York Virtuoso Singers, Calvin Weirsma and Deborah Wong, violin, Lois Martin, viola, Chris Finckel, violoncello, and Jared Egen, bass, Original file name: THE NY VIRTUOSO SINGERS.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-099 (Image-file cd06_18)
- RFBR, June 2007, VII.; 1 CD-ROM (11 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with members of the Red Fish Blue Fish percussion ensemble, Greg Stuart, Robert Esler, Gustavo Aguilar, and Justin DeHart, with technical assistant, Ian Saxton, around the Waterphone instrument used in Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: IMG_4936 copy.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-089-dup (Image-file cd07_01)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with Waterphone used in the Oracle section of his composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Reynolds THE ORACLE.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-083 (Image-file cd07_02)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with technical assistant, Ian Saxton, and members of the Red Fish Blue Fish percussion ensemble, Greg Stuart, Robert Esler, Justin DeHart, and Gustavo Aguilar, Original file name: RFBF with Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-088 (Image-file cd07_03)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble, with Johannes Fischer conducting, Matthew Jenkins, Robert Esler, Greg Stuart, and Fabio Oliveira rehearsing Aubrey Byerly's composition, …woven with a silent motto, Original file name: RFBF.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-053 (Image-file cd07_04)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble, with Johannes Fischer conducting, Matthew Jenkins, Robert Esler, Greg Stuart, and Fabio Oliveira rehearsing Aubrey Byerly's composition, …woven with a silent motto, Original file name: RFBF_.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-053-dup (Image-file cd07_05)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with members of the Red Fish Blue Fish percussion ensemble, Greg Stuart, Robert Esler, Gustavo Aguilar, and Justin DeHart, with technical assistant, Ian Saxton, around the Waterphone instrument used in Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Roger Reynolds with RFBF.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-089 (Image-file cd07_06)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with Waterphone used in his composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-082 (Image-file cd07_07)
  - Roger Reynolds talks with Steven Schick, director the Red Fish Blue Fish percussion ensemble, Original file name: Steve Schick_Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-084-dup (Image-file cd07_08)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with Waterphone used in the Oracle section of his composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: The Oracle Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-081 (Image-file cd07_09)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with Waterphone used in the Oracle section of his composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: The Oracle Roger Reynoldsb-w.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-080 (Image-file cd07_10)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Greg Stuart, Justin DeHart, Gustavo Aguilar, and Robert Esler rehearsing Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Greg Stuart, Justin DeHart, Gustavo Aguilar, and Robert Esler rehearsing Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: _RFBF.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-060-dup (Image-file cd07_11)
- Reynolds masterclass '07, June 2007, VIII.; 1 CD-ROM (5 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: Masterclass Roger Reynolds.tif (Image-file cd08_01)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: Masterclass- Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-095-dup (Image-file cd08_02)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: Masterclass-Roger Reynolds.tif (Image-file cd08_03)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: ROGER REYNOLDS Masterclass-.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-097-dup (Image-file cd08_04)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: Roger Reynolds Masterclass.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-096-dup (Image-file cd08_05)
- Lucy Shelton, June 2007, IX.; 1 CD-ROM (17 image files in TIFF format)
  - Curtis Macomber playing violin, Original file name: Curtis Macomber.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-049 (Image-file cd09_01)
  - Composers Charles Wuorinen and Roger Reynolds with soprano Lucy Shelton, Original file name: Charles 008.tif (Image-file cd09_02)
  - Soprano Lucy Shelton and violinist Curtis Macomber, Original file name: Lucy Shelton rehearsing with Curtis Macomber.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-107 (Image-file cd09_03)
  - Composers Charles Wuorinen and Roger Reynolds with soprano Lucy Shelton, Original file name: Lucy Shelton Wuorinen Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-126 (Image-file cd09_04)
  - Soprano Lucy Shelton onstage with Curtis Macomber, violin, Alan Feinberg, piano, and Nina Lee, violoncello, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 001.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-109 (Image-file cd09_05)
  - Soprano Lucy Shelton onstage with Curtis Macomber, violin, Alan Feinberg, piano, and Nina Lee, violoncello, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 002.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-110 (Image-file cd09_06)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with Lucy Shelton, soprano, Alan Feinberg, piano, and Nina Lee, violoncello, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 004.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-120 (Image-file cd09_07)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with violinist Curtis Macomber, soprano Lucy Shelton, pianist Alan Feinberg, and violoncellist Nina Lee, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 006.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-124 (Image-file cd09_08)
  - Soprano Lucy Shelton taking a bow onstage with Curtis Macomber, violin, Alan Feinberg, piano, and Nina Lee, violoncello, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 010.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-111 (Image-file cd09_09)
  - Soprano Lucy Shelton taking a bow onstage with Curtis Macomber, violin, Alan Feinberg, piano, and Nina Lee, violoncello, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 011.tif (Image-file cd09_10)
  - Soprano Lucy Shelton and violinist Curtis Macomber, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 022.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-106 (Image-file cd09_11)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with Alan Feinberg, piano, Lucy Shelton, soprano, and Nina Lee, violoncello, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 024.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-121 (Image-file cd09_12)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with violinist Curtis Macomber, pianist Alan Feinberg, soprano Lucy Shelton, and violoncellist Nina Lee, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 025.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-122 (Image-file cd09_13)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with violinist Curtis Macomber, pianist Alan Feinberg, soprano Lucy Shelton, and violoncellist Nina Lee, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 026.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-123 (Image-file cd09_14)
  - Soprano Lucy Shelton onstage with Curtis Macomber, violin, Alan Feinberg, piano, and Nina Lee, violoncello, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_ 027.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-108 (Image-file cd09_15)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with violoncellist Nina Lee, soprano Lucy Shelton, pianist Alan Feinberg, and violinist Curtis Macomber, after a performance of Wuorinen's composition, Fenton Songs II, Original file name: Lucy Shelton_Wuorinen_Macomber_Nina Lee.tif (Image-file cd09_16)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with violoncellist Nina Lee, soprano Lucy Shelton, pianist Alan Feinberg, and violinist Curtis Macomber, after a performance of Wuorinen's composition, Fenton Songs II, Original file name: Nina Lee Wuorinen Lucy Shelton Alan Feinberg Curtis Macomber.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-125 (Image-file cd09_17)
- Harbison masterclass, June 2007, X.; 1 CD-ROM (26 image files in TIFF format)
  - John Harbison with conductor Robert Franz and the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, Original file name: BPO composer John Harbison.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-023 (Image-file cd10_01)
  - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra with Robert Franz, conductor, Original file name: BPO 003.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-008 (Image-file cd10_02)
  - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra with Robert Franz, conductor, Original file name: BPO 007.tif (Image-file cd10_03)
  - David Felder, with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra and conductor Robert Franz during rehearsal of Felder's Three pieces for orchestra, Original file name: BPO and composer David Felder.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-012 (Image-file cd10_04)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with June in Buffalo students: Paolo Cavallone, John Aylward, Michael McBride, Daniel Van Hassel, Jeff Silva, Eliza Brown, and Lee Weisert, Original file name: Charles Wuorinen masterclass.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-127 (Image-file cd10_05)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen gesturing during seminar, Original file name: CHARLES Wuorinen...tif Converted file name: JIB2007-117 (Image-file cd10_06)
  - John Harbison examining score with students Aubrey Byerly, Bert Van Herck, Fusun Koksal, J.T. Rinker, and Lee Weisert, Original file name: John Harbison Masterclass.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-026 (Image-file cd10_07)
  - John Harbison in Music Library Seminar Room, Original file name: John Harbison.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-022 (Image-file cd10_08)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with June in Buffalo students: Jane Stanley, Bert Van Herck, and Matthew Barnson, Original file name: Masterclass Charles Wuorinen 07.tif (Image-file cd10_09)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: Masterclass Roger Reynolds.tif (Image-file cd10_10)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with June in Buffalo students: Paolo Cavallone, John Aylward, Michael McBride, Daniel Van Hassel, Jeff Silva, Eliza Brown, and Lee Weisert, Original file name: masterclass Wuorinen------.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-129 (Image-file cd10_11)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen presenting masterclass to students, Original file name: Masterclass Wuorinen-==.tif (Image-file cd10_12)
  - Student composers in masterclass by Charles Wuorinen, Original file name: masterclass Wuorinen....tif (Image-file cd10_13)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with June in Buffalo students: Jane Stanley, Bert Van Herck, and Matthew Barnson, Original file name: Masterclass WUORINEN.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-130 (Image-file cd10_14)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: Masterclass- Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-095 (Image-file cd10_15)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: Masterclass-Roger Reynolds.tif (Image-file cd10_16)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with June in Buffalo students, Original file name: masterclass-Wuorinen--...tif (Image-file cd10_17)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with June in Buffalo students, Original file name: masterclass-Wuorinen.tif (Image-file cd10_18)